Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1915-2010, UWM Archival Collection 48; 19 cubic ft. (23 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - Friends of Pat Lucey & M. Schrieber, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Friends of Roots Cooperative, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Friends of Spartacus Youth League, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Friends of the Arboretum, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Friends of the Association for Humanist Psychology, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Friends of the Eighth Note Coffeehouse, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Friends of the Guardian, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Friends of the Indochinese People, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Friends of the Indo-Chinese People at UWM, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Friends of the Milwaukee Tenant Union, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Friends of the Rap House, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Friends of the UWM Union Art Gallery, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Friends of Women's Transit Service, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Fritz Blitz, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - "From the Dean's Den," 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Full Gospel Assembly, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Gamers Guild, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Gamma Delta
    - 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Gamma Delta Iota, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Gamma Phi Beta, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Gamma Sigma Sigma, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Gamma Theta Delta, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Gamma Theta Upsilon
    - 1957-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1957-1988 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Financial Records, 1949-1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1950-1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Programs, 1950-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook, 1950-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Gay Christian Outreach, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Gay Peoples Union, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Gay Students Association, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Gelmetal Movement Company, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - General Semantics, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Geography Club, 1944-1959 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Geography Graduate Students Association, 1974-1984 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Geology Club, 1964, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Geophysical Society, 1975-1985 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - German Club, 1939-1963 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Gibbons Club, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Global Outreach, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Golf Club, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Good Government, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Good Kids at UWM, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Government in Gear, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Graduate Business Association, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Graduate Social Work Club, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Graduate Student Organization, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Graduate Students in Education, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Graduates in Nursing, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Greater Opportunities, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Greek Student Association, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Greek Week, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Green Party, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Group Against Smokers' Pollution, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Group Jay, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Groupo Estaudiantil Puertorriqueno, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Guide for Social Chairmen, 1960s (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Guide for Student Organizations, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Guidon, 1966-1979 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Guild Student Group, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Gurdjieff -Nyland Milwaukee Group, 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Gymnastics Club, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Half-Baked Theater Troupe, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hamagshimim, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Handball Club, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Handicapped Students League, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hang Gliding Club, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Harris for President-UWM, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Health Center Advisory Board, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Hellas Greek Student Association, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Hispanic Graduate Student Association, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Hispanic Intellectuals of Milwaukee, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Hispanic Student Alliance, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - History Club, 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - History Graduate Assistants Club, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Holiday Singers, 1958-1966 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Holton Hall
    - 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 1969 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Homecoming, 1958-1977 (Box 4, Folder 8-11)
  - Homosexual Freedom League, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Honor Societies of the College, 1953-1957, undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Honoratae, Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Honoratae Senior Women's Honor Society Responds to Mortar Board Questionnaire, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Hot Air Ballooning Club, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - House Party, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Housing Rules, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Human Relations Council, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Human Rights Organization, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Humans Advocating Humor and Amusement, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Hunger Project at UWM, 1981-1986 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Ibero-American Studies Society, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Imagen Latina, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Improving our Union (IOU), 1994 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Independent Coalition, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Independent Election Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Independent, Responsible Students (I.R.S.), 1994 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Independent Student Opportunities, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Independents for McCarthy, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - India Cultural Society, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Indian Community Day Care, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Indian Student Association, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Inner-City Community Resources, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Inter-Arts League 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Inter-Cultural Association, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Inter-Greek Council, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Inter-Normal Forensic League, 1930-1932 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Inter-Sorority Council, 1947-1957 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Intercampus, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Intercollegiate Association of Women Students, 1960-1975 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Intercollegiate Knights, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Interdorm Council, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Interested Veterans of Central City, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1947-1981 (Box 4, Folder 29-31)
  - Interfraternity Council, Activities, 1966-1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - International Associatioin of Business Communications, 1988-1994 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - International Business Students Association, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - International Cultural Club, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - International Folk Dancers at UWM, 1975-1985 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - International Friendship Ministry, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - International Greek Expansion Council, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - International Muslim Student Organization, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - International Relations Club, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - International Students Club, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - International Television Association, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Investment Finance Group, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Iota Chi Sorority, 1968-1978 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Iranian Students Organization, 1974-1990 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Islamic Information Service, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Israeli Student Organization, 1972-1981 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Ivy Publications, 1957-1969 (Box 4, Folder 39-40)
  - Japanese Karate Club at UWM, 1979-1986 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Jazz Street, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Jesse Jackson for President '88, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Jesus People, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Jewish Student Movement, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Jewish Student Union, 1981-1994 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Jim Wood for Governor, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - John Brown Revolutionary Brigade, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - John Tudor Fan Club, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Johnston Hall, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Johnston Hall, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Joseph Conrad Club, undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Jude III, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Judo Club, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Judo-Kodokan Judo Klub, 1969-1991 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Judo Team at UWM, 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Juggling Society at UWM, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Junior American Pharmaceutical Association, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Junior Class, 1953-1957 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Justice & Peace Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Kappa Delta Pu, 1958-1982 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Kappa Lambda Iota, 1950-1958 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Kappa Upsilon Nu Tau, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Karate Club, 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Kennedy for President, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Kenwood Hall, 1949-1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Kindergarten Primary Association, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Krishna Yoga Society, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Krishnamurti Club at UWM, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - L5 at UWM, 1978-1982 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - La Colectiva, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - La Onda Latina, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Labor Farm Party, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Lambda Chi Alpha, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Lambda Phi Chi, 1954-1959 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Laotian-American Student Association, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Latin Club, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Latinos Unidos, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Latter Day Saints Student Association, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Lavender Commitment, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - League of United Latin American Citizens, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Letterman's Club, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Liaison Social Service Organization, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Liberal Club, 1961-1965, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Liberal Programmers, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Life Sciences Organization, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Lifesaving Corps, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Literary Club at UWM, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Living Art Exhibition, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Los Universitarios, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Lutheran Collegians, 1965-1986 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Lutheran Student Association of Metropolitan Milwaukee, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lutheran Student Fellowship, 1968-1993 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Lutheran Students Association, 1938-1940 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - M & G Social Club, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Macintosh Users Group at UWM, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Magic Lantern Film Society, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Majority Coalition, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Make Opportunity Available Now, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Malaysian Business and Liberal Arts Association, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Malaysian Student Association, 1982-1994 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Margaret-Mary Ann Pageant Dancers, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Marietta House, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Mario Cuomo for President, 1988, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Market Reach, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Marketiers of UWM, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Marketing Club, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Martial Arts Club, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Marxists in Academia, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Masada, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Masters Swim Club, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Math Club, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Mathematics Club, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - McCarthy for President Club, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - McLaren Hall, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - McLaren Hall Association, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Medical Club, 1919-1922 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Medical Technologists Club, 1965-1981 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Medieval Gaming Association, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Meditation Society at UWM, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Meeting of the Mimes, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Meher Baba Information, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Member of Science Society, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Men's Chorus, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Men's Glee Club, 1930, 1958-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Men's Physical Education Club, 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Men's Press Club, 1964, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Mid-Continental Model United Nations Program, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Middle East Coalition Against Violence and Racism, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Military Council at UWM, 1962-1985 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Milwaukee Adventure Gaming Society, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Milwaukee Alliance, 1973-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Milwaukee Area Jewish Independent Coalition, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Milwaukee Area Nonviolent Direct Action Committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Milwaukee Betar, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Milwaukee Cardinals Pep Club, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Milwaukee Citizen's Drug Prevention Ad Hoc Committee, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Milwaukee Coalition for Choice at UWM, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Milwaukee Committee for American-Soviet Friendship, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Milwaukee Educational Society, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Milwaukee Graduate Assistants Association, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Milwaukee Hunger Hike, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Milwaukee Intercollegiate Civil Liberties Union, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Milwaukee Liberation Front, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Milwaukee Organizing Committee, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Milwaukee People's Office, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Milwaukee Rebirth Association, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Milwaukee Road Review, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Milwaukee Square Dancers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Milwaukee Student Chapter of the APA, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Milwaukee Student Peace Union, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Milwaukee Students Association, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Milwaukee Undergraduate Review, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Milwaukee Women's Rugby Football Club, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Minorities for Wood, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Minority Business Students Association, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Minority Coalition, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Mixed Chorus, 1958-1962 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Mixed Media, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Model United Nations, 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Mondale/Ferraro, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Montessorian, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Mortar Board, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Mortar Board, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Motor Sports Association, 1967-1974 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Movement for a New Congress, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - MSW Club at UWM, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Mu Beta Sigma, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Mu Epsilon Pi, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Mu Kappa Tau (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Mural, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Music Educator's National Conference, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Music Entertainment Association, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Music From Almost Yesterday, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Music Students Association, 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Music Therapy Organization, 1969-1990 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Music Through Action, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Music With Percussion Ensemble, 1974-1990 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Muslim Youth, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - NA Recovery at UWM, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - NAACP, 1957-1994 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Narcotics Anonymous, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Nation Every Nation, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - National and International Student Congress, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - National Art Education Association (NAEA), 1976-1986 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - National Assocation of Black Journalists, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - National Broadcasting Society - Alpha Epsilon Rho, 1980-1993 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - National Campus Film Network/Dream on Film Series, 1982-1990 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - National Collegiate Players, 1963-1972 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - National Honor Society, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - National Jazz Fraternity, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - National Society of Pershing Rifles, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - National Student Association, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Navigators at UWM, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Negative Movement, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - New Age Bible Study, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - New Age Party, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - New American Movement
    - 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - undated (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - New Community at UWM, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - New Directions, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - New Edition, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - New Era, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - New Fenians, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - New Media Club, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - New Party at UWM, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Newman Club, 1957-1970 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Nigerian Student Organization, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - None of the Above, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Non-Partisan Party, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Notable Organization for Valued Academics (ANOVA), 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Northpoint Junior Investment Club, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - NSA Club of UWM, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Nu Digamma Phi (New Warrior Fraternity), 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Nurses Professional Organization, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - OA at UWM, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - October 23 Coalition, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Off Campus Student Residence Location Study, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Ojibwemo Society, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Omega Club, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Omega Community Service Organization, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Omega Pearl Club, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Omicron Mu, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Oratorio Chorus, 1958-1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Order of Artus, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Organ Guild, 1959-1977 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Organization for Students of Objectivism, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Organization for the Learning Disabled at UWM, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Organization of Justice, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 113)
  - Organization of Professionals Help, Crisis Referral Line, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 114)
  - Organization of School Psychology, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Organized Rock Climbers, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - ORO - Macedonian Folk Ensemble, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Othello Club at UWM, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Orthodox Campus Fellowship, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 115)
  - Orthodox Christian Fellowship, 1970-1987 (Box 18, Folder 116)
  - Out To Lunch Party, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Outing Club, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Outing Council, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Padarewski Club, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Pail and Shovel, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 117)
  - Pakistani Student Association, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 118)
  - Paleontological Society of UWM, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 119)
  - Palestine Liberation Support Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Panhellenic Ball Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Panhellenic Council
    - 1960-1971 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Housing, 1958-1970 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Rush, 1952-1967 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Panther Booster Club, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Panther Courier, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Panther Dive Club, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 120)
  - Panther Football Club, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 121)
  - Panther Herald, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 122)
  - Panther Party of UWM, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Panther Pep Club, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Panther Platoon, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 123)
  - Panther Publishers, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 124)
  - Panther Soccer Club, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Panther Travel, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 125)
  - Panthers for Pep, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Para-Psychological Society, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Pat Paulsen Intranational Peace Party, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Pax Christi Catholic Peace Movement, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Peace Through Law, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Peak Night
    - 1947-1964 (Box 11, Folder 37-39)
    - Programs, 1938-1967 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Pedal for the Homeless, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 126)
  - People for Dennis Conta, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - People for Improved Education, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - People for Unspecified Stuff, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 127)
  - People United for Integration & Quality Education, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Peoples Consciousness Front, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 128)
  - People's Daily World Readers Club, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 129)
  - People's Party Student Organization, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - People's Peace Treaty, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Pershing Rifles
    - 1958-1970 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - 1958-1990 (Box 18, Folder 130)
  - Phantasy Films, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Pharmaceutical Society, 1957-1974 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Phi Alpha Theta, 1953-1962 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Phi Beta Kappa
    - 1964, 1973-1978, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - 1973-1974, undated (Box 18, Folder 131)
  - Phi Beta Rho, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Phi Chi Theta, 1966-1973 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Phi Delta Delta, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Phi Delta Epsilon, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1958-1967 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Phi Eta Sigma, 1956-1963 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Phi Gamma Delta, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Phi Gamma Nu, 1966-1976 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1961-1990 (Box 18, Folder 132)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Phi Lambda Theta, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Phi Mu, 1957-1974 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Phi Mu Alpha Sinfonia, 1957-1975 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Phi Mu Sigma, 1956-1970 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Phi Sigma Delta
    - 1956-1969 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Phi Sigma Epsilon
    - 1950-1969 (Box 11, Folder 47-48)
    - 1957-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Phi Sigma Sigma
    - 1955-1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1970 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Phi Tau, 1968-1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Philatelic Society, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Philocophia Club, 1917-1956 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Philocophia Club, Scrapbook, 1945-1957 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Philosophical Circle, 1959-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Philosophers Anonymous, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 133)
  - Philosophical Association at UWM, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 134)
  - Philosophy Club, 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Photographers for a Democratic Society, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Physical Education Majors and Minors Club, 1961-1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Pi Lambda Theta, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Pi Lambda Theta
    - 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - 1959-1991 (Box 18, Folder 135)
  - Pi Sigma Alpha, 1976-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Pi Sigma Epsilon, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Pinkos, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Planning Documents, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Player's Association, 1979-1986 (Box 18, Folder 136)
  - Playrs 'O, 1988-1995 (Box 18, Folder 137)